Little Magazine Collection, 1895-1976 (bulk 1965-1976)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Wordjock, West Lafayette, Indiana, v. 1, #3, May, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 17)
- Wordjock, Albert Lea, Minnesota, #4, November, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 18)
- Wordjock, Ganges, Canada, #5 (and Earthwords 1), April, 1970 (Box 57, Folder 19)
- Workshop, London, England, #9, undated (Box 57, Folder 20)
- Workshop, London, England, #10, undated (Box 57, Folder 21)
- Workshop, London, England, #11, undated (Box 57, Folder 22)
- Workshop, London, England, #12, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 23)
- Workshop, London, England, #13, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 24)
- Workshop, London, England, #14, undated (Box 57, Folder 25)
- The World, New York City, #3, May, 1967 (Box 57, Folder 26)
- The World, New York City, #9, December, 1967 (Box 57, Folder 27)
- The World, New York City, #11, April, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 28)
- The World, New York City, #13, November, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 29)
- The World, New York City, #15, part 1, March, 1969 (Box 57, Folder 30)
- The World, New York City, #15, part 2, March, 1969 (Box 57, Folder 31)
- The World, New York City, #17, November, 1969-December, 1969 (Box 57, Folder 32)
- The World, New York City, #18, February, 1970-March, 1970 (Box 58, Folder 1)
- The World, New York City, #19, May, 1970 (Box 58, Folder 2)
- The World, New York City, #20, October, 1970 (Box 58, Folder 3)
- The World, New York City, #21, January, 1971 (Box 58, Folder 4)
- The World, New York City, #22, April, 1970 (Box 58, Folder 5)
- The World, New York City, #23, Summer, 1971 (Box 58, Folder 6)
- The World, New York City, #25, 1972 (Box 58, Folder 7)
- The World, New York City, #26, Winter, 1973 (Box 58, Folder 8)
- The World, New York City, #27, April 4, 1973 (Box 58, Folder 9)
- The World, New York City, #30, July, 1976 (Box 58, Folder 10)
- Writer's Forum, New York City, v. 2, #3, Summer, 1966 (Box 58, Folder 11)
- Writer's Workshop, California Labor School, San Francisco, #2, Spring, 1953 (Box 58, Folder 12)
- Writing/Georgia Straight, Vancouver, Canada, #1, circa October, 1969-November, 1969 (Box 58, Folder 13)
- Writing/Georgia Straight, Vancouver, Canada, #2 (Jack Spicer), January 28, 1970-February 4, 1970 (Box 58, Folder 14)
- Writing/Georgia Straight, Vancouver, Canada, #3, April 1, 1970-April 8, 1970 (Box 58, Folder 15)
- Writing/Georgia Straight, Vancouver, Canada, #4, May 6, 1970-May 13, 1970 (Box 58, Folder 16)
- Writing/Georgia Straight, Vancouver, Canada, #5, September 30-October 6, 1970 (Box 58, Folder 17)
- Wurm, Pretoria, South Africa, #9, July, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 18)
- Wurm, Pretoria, South Africa, #11, April, 1969 (Box 58, Folder 19)
- Xanadu, Wantagh, New York, v. 2, #1, Fall, 1976 (Box 59, Folder 1)
- Xilote, Mexico, October, 1971 (Box 59, Folder 2)
- Yale Poetry Review, New Haven, Connecticut, #8, 1948 (Box 59, Folder 3)
- The Yale Review, New Haven, Connecticut, v. 51, #2, December, 1961 (Box 59, Folder 4)
- Yanagi, Sausalito, California, #2, April, 1975 (Box 59, Folder 5)
- Yankee Poetry Chapbook, Flushing, Long Island, New York, Summer, 1934 (Box 59, Folder 6)
- Yes, Montreal, Canada, v. 2, #2, Summer, 1957 (Box 59, Folder 7)
- Yes, Pierrefonds, Canada, #17 (2nd series), October, 1969 (Box 59, Folder 8)
- Yugen, New York City, #2, 1958 (Box 59, Folder 9)
- Yugen, New York City, #3, 1958 (Box 59, Folder 10)
- Yugen, New York City, #4, 1959 (Box 59, Folder 11)
- Yugen, New York City, #8, 1962 (Box 59, Folder 12)
- Zahir, Durham, New Hampshire, v. 1, #1, Winter, 1970 (Box 59, Folder 13)
- Zahir, Durham, New Hampshire, v. 1, #3, Fall, 1971 (Box 59, Folder 14)
- Zahir, Durham, New Hampshire, v. 1, #4-5, 1972 (Box 59, Folder 15)
- Zahir, Newbury, Massachusetts, v. 1, #6, 1974 (Box 59, Folder 16)
- Zahir, Newburyport, Massachusetts, v. 2, #1 (#7), 1975 (Box 59, Folder 17)
- Zahir, Newburyport, Massachusetts, v. 2, #2 (#8), 1976 (Box 59, Folder 18)
- Zeitgeist, East Lansing, Michigan, v. 2, #3, March, 1968-April, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 19)
- Zeitgeist, East Lansing, Michigan, v. 3, #1, Autumn, 1969 (Box 59, Folder 20)
- 0 to 9, New York City, April, 1967 (Box 59, Folder 21)
- 0 to 9, New York City, #2, August, 1967 (Box 59, Folder 22)
- 0 to 9, New York City, #3, January, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 23)
- 0 to 9, New York City, #4, June, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 24)
- 0 to 9, New York City, #5, January, 1969 (Box 59, Folder 25)
- Ziggurat, Milwaukee, Wisconsin, v. 1, #1, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 26)
- Confluence, Lindenwood College, Saint Charles, Missouri, October, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 1)
- The Hasty Papers, New York City, December, 1960 (Box 60, Folder 2)
- The Orange Bear Reader, Windsor, Canada, #1 (Paul Goodman), undated (Box 60, Folder 3)
- The Orange Bear Reader, Windsor, Canada, #2 (Joyce Carol Oates), undated (Box 60, Folder 4)
- The Orange Bear Reader, Windsor, Canada, #3 (Douglas Blazek), undated (Box 60, Folder 5)
- The Orange Bear Reader, Windsor, Canada, #4 (Irving Layton), undated (Box 60, Folder 6)
- The Orange Bear Reader, Windsor, Canada, #5 (Greg Kuzma), undated (Box 60, Folder 7)
- The Orange Bear Reader, Windsor, Canada, #7 (George Bowering), undated (Box 60, Folder 8)
- The Orange Bear Reader, Windsor, Canada, #8 (Lewis Warsh), undated (Box 60, Folder 9)
- The Orange Bear Reader, Windsor, Canada, #9 (Hayden Carruth), undated (Box 60, Folder 10)